So they're here.
Yes.
The humans who were captured by the
demon king as slaves and their children.
The demon king is known to be
ruthlessly coldhearted and cruel.
Who knows what kind of horrible
torture they're suffering?
I see.
All the more reason
we must help them.
Leave it all to me, Merryna!
Hey!
Oh, Doux!
Let's play, everyone!
We've been waiting for you!
What should we play today?
Hm, let's see...
Let's play at the park
the grownups made for us!
Okay, it's settled!
SANTA IS HANDING OUT TOO MANY PRESENTS!!
"Santa Is Handing Out Too Many Presents!!"
"LET'S PLAY, LA, LA, LA"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: TAKERU TAKEMIYA
SONG: DOUX
Experts at playing, gather around
Gather all your hands to me
Where are we? This is everyone's park
Whoosh, whoosh, we
become the wind on this slide
Swing, swing, we're flying through
the air on these swings
La, la, la-la-la
La, la, la, la, la
It's so fun if we all play together
La, la, la-la-la
La, la, la, la, la
Let's all play again tomorrow
Santa Claus?
Yeah. Santa shows up on Christmas
night after we all fall asleep.
They leave all the good kids
something they wanted as
a gift at their pillows.
Wow! That's amazing! So when's Christmas?
It's actually today.
So Santa Claus is coming?!
Are they not?
You have to write down your name and
what you want on paper so Santa knows
or they won't come.
But...
we don't have any paper here
or anything to write with.
Okay! Leave it to Doux!
So...
That's why you came to
get a pen and some paper.
Yup! Sure did!
What do you think about
this, Your Majesty?
Let her be, Jahi.
There's no harm in giving
the slaves pen and paper.
How naïve.
You mustn't underestimate what
pen and paper can be used for.
As you can see, it can
be used as a weapon.
I see.
DOUX
Here, use this instead.
They're much softer.
Okay!
Your Majesty!
What do you want me to do?
Santa Claus! Santa Claus!
Just look at how much she's
looking forward to this.
How am I supposed to tell her no now?
Well, don't worry so much.
I've heard of this Santa character.
According to the legends...
They apparently have the power
to materialize any wish.
But...
There's no way such a great being exists.
If they did, we demons would've
been destroyed ages ago.
You are correct.
Right?
If such a great being actually exists,
then they will prove to
be a great asset to us.
Why, yes... hm?
Lady Doux!
We shall capture this Santa Claus and
make them His Majesty's subordinate!
Huh?
This is the Capture Santa Trial!
Okay!
Hm?
Now, please allow me to explain this plan.
Okay, Teacher!
According to our intel,
Santa comes by at night
after everyone is asleep.
Yup, yup!
First, let us head to the
mines and hide in the shadows.
And once everyone is asleep, we
shall use transparency magic,
completely conceal ourselves,
and await Santa.
Santa will arrive, being none the wiser,
and then His Majesty will entrap them in
a binding barrier so they cannot escape.
Wait, I'm participating in this, too?
Then Lady Doux will immobilize
them with her ice magic
and our mission will be complete!
Complete!
What do you think of
this plan, Your Majesty?
Er, what do I think?
So excited! So excited!
It's a brilliant plan!
Yay!
Thank you very much, Your Majesty!
Lady Doux, let us have those human
children write letters immediately
to lure Santa in!
Yeah!
I'm certain Santa doesn't exist,
but this is so endearing that
I'll just watch over them.
Thanks, Doux.
Do you think Santa Claus will come?
Yeah, they will!
I'm gonna ask for cake!
I'm gonna ask for toys!
So many wishes!
What are you going to ask for, Doux?
Hm...
I know!
Hup!
The prank was a huge success...
Where are the children?
How could you get lost in
the demon king's castle?
Well, you said to go this way, Tontt.
Let's hurry up and find them.
We'll be in trouble if the demons wake up.
We'll be fine. Those who hear Santa's
bell won't wake up for a while.
You say that but your non-existent
boobs are shaking.
How about I feed you
to one of these demons?
Caught you, Santa Claus!
Whoa!
Boo!
A-A child?!
Everyone else fell asleep,
so I came all by myself.
Wh-What?! Who is this?!
I'm Doux! Doux the demon!
A-A demon?!
Take this!
I thought any creature other than
Santa was supposed to sleep
when they heard this sound!
Why are you awake?!
Doux stayed up late!
Aw, what a naughty little girl.
Doux is a bad girl!
Santa's been won over by a demon?!
Are you really Santa Claus, miss?
Yes, I really am Santa Claus.
And this is Tontt the gnome.
Tontt?
I know, Doux.
We have to hand out some presents.
Do you know where the children are?
Huh? Wait...
I do! Doux wants to hand them out, too!
Huh?
There's something very wrong with this.
Can you take this one, too?
Yup!
You're having a demon help
you hand out presents!
Shh.
Doux is a good girl.
She's a demon!
She might just be getting your
guard down so she can strike.
Well, you were originally
a demon, too, Tontt.
That's true, but...
Tontt's a demon?
Yes. Tontt is the name of my many helpers.
There's a lot of them?
Yes. The Tontts were
demons who created toys
and caused mischief for
humans in their attics.
But...
On a very cold night long ago,
a Tontt was trying to steal some
food and was found by a child.
They escaped into the attic
but became unable to move
from starvation and the cold.
That's when it happened.
The child who found the Tontt brought
them some warm milk and cookies.
Then they snuggled up
in a blanket together.
It was a cold night, but they
were able to sleep nice and warm.
That Tontt had a change of heart and
wondered if they could do something
for that good child and
other good children.
And then... they became Santa Claus!
They got big!
Which means when Tontts grow up...
They turn out like this!
Wow!
Once they become Santa,
they can create anything.
Wow! That's amazing!
Then there's a lot of Santa Clauses?
Yes.
Then...
Are there Santas that look like this?
Oh, what a lovely drawing.
This one looks just like my older brother.
He'll get mad at you for saying that.
Did you draw all of this, Doux?
Nope. Doux drew this one.
Den drew this one, and Sana drew this one.
Doux, you're a demon. Why are
you doing that with humans?
Because we're friends!
Friends?
Yup!
I see.
And...
Wh-What is it?
Merryna and Tontt are also my friends!
Really? That makes Santa so happy!
Then if you meet another Santa or Tontt,
be friends with them, too, okay?
Yeah!
Okay, just three more
presents to hand out.
To finish things off, let's see who can
deliver theirs the fastest!
Huh?
Ready...
go!
This is so childish...
But what else can I do?
All done!
Yay! Mission complete!
Doux, thank you for helping me out.
Yay!
Oh, are you going home already?
Yes. Before I go, why don't
I grant your wish, Doux?
I'm just supposed to do this for human
children, but let me grant you a wish.
What's your wish, Doux?
Doux's wish...
I WANT TO HELP SANTA CLAUS
-DOUX
already came true though.
So that's why you were awake?
Thank you.
Can we talk again sometime?
Yes. I'm sure we can.
Make sure you stay a good
girl until then, okay?
Yup.
Merry Christmas!
You met Santa Claus?!
Yup. She was a lady Santa.
H-How could I fall asleep
at a time like that?
We handed out presents together.
We completed our mission!
To think they actually existed...
The world is bigger than I thought.
S-So where is this Santa?
Did you capture her?!
Nope. She went home.
No... It's not "mission complete"
if you didn't capture her...
But she gave me a present.
Look! It's a big box!
I wonder what's inside.
All right, Doux!
Now your trial is to capture Santa Jahi!
One, two! One, two!
One, two! Mission complete!
THE DEMON KING'S FAMILIAR LOVES HUMANS TOO MUCH!!
"The Demon King's Familiar
Loves Humans Too Much!!"
A wall in the mines collapsed?
Yes. Apparently, there are some
human casualties, as well.
Casualties?
Er, this doesn't concern you, Doux.
More importantly, it's dangerous
if you aren't being careful.
Okay!
What were you supposed to do
with your left hand again?
Hm...
Oh! Curl it up like a kitty paw!
That's right, a kitty paw.
Meow, meow!
Very good.
Okay, now let's slowly cut that
with the knife. Slowly, okay?
Slowly!
Be careful with that knife, okay?
If you cut your hand, it's
going to be really ouchy!
Slowly, slowly.
There, there, there.
You're so overprotective!
Hiyah.
No! You've got the wrong idea, Jahi!
How do I have the wrong idea?!
You are absolutely, positively
overprotectively showing her how to cook!
I figured this might happened,
so I declined at first.
However...
You know...
You and Big Sister Jahi
are busy with work, right?
So Doux wants to get really good
at cooking and make you yummy food!
How am I supposed to decline
after she says something like that?
My precious daughter's
first homemade meal!
Please cut us a little slack, Jahi.
I fear that it might be too late for him.
Eat up!
This does look delicious.
Oh, no. His Majesty is devastated
she didn't offer him
her first homemade meal!
Say, "Aah!"
Should I eat this? Should I not?
Which one is it?!
You don't like sandwiches?
N-No, I wouldn't say that...
Actually, Lady Doux!
Let's prepare some food for
the magical beasts, too!
For the magical beasts?
I see. That's a brilliant idea.
Then why don't you feed my familiar?
It'd be perfect for that trial.
Yes, as you wish.
Giant rocks!
A part of the wall collapsed.
Because of that, the
mining has been halted.
Not to mention...
Human casualties like that also occurred.
Wait! Don't go rush off to treat them!
But they can't work if I don't heal them.
How do you always think like that?
Did you forget the three principles
to become a full-fledged demon?
Mushrooms, seal, and... chill?
You must shrewdly
oppress, steal, and kill.
Demons are supposed to
be cruel and hurt humans.
And we aren't supposed to treat
humans who are already injured.
We're supposed to feed
them to the monsters.
This is Druj.
His Majesty's one and only familiar.
Druj contributed greatly while His
Majesty was trying to conquer the world
Druj proved most useful...
when it came to getting rid of
the defeated humans.
Druj reacts to human blood
and only eats the wounded.
The wounded?
Yes. Meaning...
We are going to feed that human to Druj.
That is your trial for today, Lady Doux.
But Doux wants to help
the humans' ouchies.
So you're saying that you are going
to abandon Druj and help the humans.
It's not just Druj.
There are many who live
in the demon world:
those who only eat meat,
those who only eat fish,
and those who only consume eggs.
They aren't picky eaters.
That is all they can eat.
Druj does not recognize anything
other than the wounded as food
and will throw anything else up.
The more you treat humans, Lady Doux,
the less Druj will have to eat.
And then Druj will die.
I don't want that to happen!
Of course, you don't.
Now, bring that wounded human over here.
Lady Doux is too kind...
So I'll just have to take
advantage of that kindness.
Demons or humans...
When faced with a situation where
she can only save one or the other,
even Lady Doux should be
able to abandon the humans.
That is what I've discovered this time.
Then we'll just have to recreate
this situation over and over
and if she gets used to abandoning them,
her attachment to the
humans should disappear.
This is the first step towards that goal.
Come with me.
Wait, I can't...
My leg is hurt. It hurts so
bad that I can't stand up.
Well, I can't take you if you can't stand.
Lady Doux?!
Why are you healing her?! I told
you not to heal her, didn't I?!
But I can't take her with
me if she can't walk.
Then you need to make them walk
even if you have to drag them!
That's what demons do!
But Doux isn't strong at all.
And my arms are all heavy,
so I can't drag her.
Your arms are heavy? Why is that?
'Cause I got lots of
sandwiches in my pockets.
That's why?!
Well, now what are you going to do?
Druj has nothing to eat and is angry now.
Try this.
I've got lots!
That won't work, Lady Doux.
I told you this already. Druj
will only eat wounded humans.
Huh?
OM NOM NOM
Really?!
Big Sister Jahi! Druj said it was yummy!
I-Impossible...
That's... mana?
D-Don't tell me Lady Doux used her
magical powers so Druj could eat it...
How can that be?
Doux decided!
D-Decided what, exactly?
Doux wants to make yummy food
that everyone can eat after all.
Demons, humans, magical
beasts, and animals!
Then they'll all tell me it's
yummy, and we can all eat together!
I-I knew it...
Great job!
You're amazing, Doux!
Druj is awesome, too!
How did this happen?
I haven't the slightest...
Someone, please tell me.